{
    "id": "0a9b97053f80420abdb519091ed46732",
    "title": "Present and Past Participle Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His ………………… coat needs mending.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tattered",
                "tattering"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "88bef57451fb4bbaa1e93ffe04d3178c"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ………………. stone gathers no moss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rolling",
                "rolled"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f8940dcfa26404388ee039d3692efd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ……………….. opportunity never returns.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "losing",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0fd6ffb025e742d289757d66d2169b3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He kept me ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waiting",
                "waited"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4d9805874cbd433ca403208c43350c24"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looked ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worried",
                "worrying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ecff45bb6d7c4a2288e69ff6cd0b6b05"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw the storm ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "approaching",
                "approached"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e6302b86d25416b8a8f0a075b83b0df"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… a noise, I turned around.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8cb999e9adaa46d188032d9b32fca272"
        },
        {
            "question": "Being ………………….., he quit his job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dissatisfied",
                "dissatisfying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "60a65cc9be6f4116baaf543b3434d47b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Being ………………… with work, I couldn’t meet them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occupied",
                "occupying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c288364ef05478489eac03e26ffc393"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. by his wife, he persevered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Encouraged",
                "Encouraging"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7b3ed6d91854160b6c0d7b15f6770b0"
        }
    ]
}